Checking outputs before showing them to users can be important for ensuring the quality,
在向用户展示之前检查输出结果，对于确保
relevance and safety of the responses provided to them or used in automation flows.
提供给用户或在自动化流程中使用的内容
的质量、相关性和安全性是很重要的。
We'll learn how to use the moderation API, but this time for outputs,
我们将学习如何使用审查API，
但这次是针对输出内容，
and how to use additional prompts to the model to evaluate output quality before displaying them.
以及如何在显示之前使用额外的
Prompt，让模型评估输出质量。
So let's dive into the examples.
让我们深入了解这些示例。
Now let's revisit it in the context of checking outputs.
现在让我们在检查输出的背景下重新审视它。
Moderation API can also be used to filter and moderate outputs generated by the system itself.
审查API还可以用于过滤和
审查系统生成的内容。
And so here's an example.
所以这里有一个例子。
So here's a generated response to the user.
这里有一个生成给用户的输出内容。
And we're going to use the moderation API in the same way that we saw in the earlier video.
使用审查API的方法跟之前
视频介绍的方法一样。
So let's see if this output is flagged.
让我们看看这个输出是否被标记。
which makes sense given the response.
这对于给定的回应是有道理的。
In general, it can also be important to check the outputs.
通常，检查输出也很重要。
For example, if you were creating a chatbot for sensitive audiences, you could use lower thresholds for flagging outputs.
例如，如果您为敏感受众创建聊天机器人，
您可以使用较低的阈值来标记输出。
In general, if the moderation output indicates that the content is flagged,
总的来说，如果审查输出内
容后，表明内容被标记，
you can take appropriate action such as responding with a fallback answer or generating a new response.
您可以采取适当的行动，比如返回一个备
用答案，或重新生成一个新的结果。
Note that as we improve the models, they also are becoming less and less likely to return some kind of harmful output.
请注意，随着模型的改进，返回某种
有害内容的概率会越来越低。
Another approach for checking outputs is to ask the model itself
另一种检查输出的方法是直接询问模型自己
if the generated was satisfactory and if it follows a certain rubric that you define.
对生成的是否令人满意，是否
符合您定义的某种标准。
This can be done by providing the generated output as part of the input to the model
实现的方式是：将模型输出的内容配合
适当的Prompt提交给模型来评估，
and asking it to rate the quality of the output.
要求模型评估输出的质量。
You can do this in various different ways.
您可以用各种不同的方式来实现这一点。
So our system message is,
我们的系统消息是：
you are an assistant  evaluates whether customer service agent responses sufficiently answer customer questions
“您是一个助手，评估客户服务代表的
回答是否充分解答了客户的问题
and also validates that all the facts the assistant cites from the product information are correct.
并验证助手引用的所有产品
信息中的事实是否正确。
The product information and user and customer service agent messages will be delimited by three backticks.
产品信息以及用户和客户服务代表的
消息将由三个反引号进行分割。
Respond with a Y or N character with no punctuation.
请用Y或N字符回答，不要加标点符号。
Y if the output sufficiently answers the question and the response correctly uses product information and no otherwise.
如果输出充分回答了问题，并且回应正
确使用了产品信息，则为Y，否则为N。
Output a single letter only.
仅输出一个字母。”
This might be a little bit difficult for the model to validate both in one step.
对于模型来说，一步验证这两个可能有点困难。
So you could play around with this.
你可以试着玩玩这个。
You could also add some other kind of guidelines.
你还可以添加其他类型的指南。
You could ask, give a rubric like a rubric for an exam or grading an essay.
你可以问，给一个类似于考试
或评分论文的评分标准。
You could use that kind of format and say,
你可以使用这种格式说：
does this use a friendly tone in line with our brand guidelines
“这是否使用了符合我们品
牌指南的友好语气？”
and maybe outline some of your brand guidelines if that's something that's very important to you.
如果这对你来说非常重要，也许
可以概述一下你的品牌指南。
So let's add our customer message.
接下来让我们添加客户留言。
So this is the initial message used to generate this response.
这是用来生成这条回复的初始留言。
And then let's also paste in our product information.
然后让我们粘贴产品信息。
And so this is the product information we fetched in the previous step for all of the products mentioned in this message.
这是我们在之前为了生成这条留言
，获取的所有产品的产品信息。
And now we'll define our comparison.
现在我们来定义对比。
So the customer message is the customer message, the product information, and then the agent response,
"Customer Message"是客户留言，产
品信息，然后是代理返回结果，
which is the response to the customer that we have from this previous cell.
这是我们从前面的单元格得
到的对客户的返回结果。
So let's format this into a messages list and get the response from the model.
让我们把这个格式化成一个消息列表，
看看从模型中得到什么样的结果。
So the model says, yes, the product information is correct and the question is answered sufficiently.
模型说：“是的”。产品信息是正确的
，问题已经得到了充分的回答。
Well, in general, for these kind of evaluation tasks,
嗯，总的来说，对于这类评估任务，
I also think it is better to use a more advanced model because they're just better at reasoning.
我认为使用更高级的模型会更好，
因为它们在推理方面更强大。
So something like GPT-4.
比如说GPT-4。
Let's try another example.
我们再试一个例子。
So this response is, life is like a box of chocolates.
这个回答是：“生活就像一盒巧克力。”
And the model has determined that this does not sufficiently answer the question or use the retrieved information.
模型已经判断出这个回答没有充分回答
问题，或者没有使用检索到的信息。
which is making up things that aren't true.
幻觉是指编造一些不真实的事情。
So as you can see, the model can provide feedback on the quality of a generated output.
如您所见，模型可以对生成
输出的质量提供反馈。
You could even experiment with generating multiple model responses per user query,
您甚至可以尝试针对每个用户
查询生成多个模型的结果，
and then having the model choose the best one to show the user.
然后让模型选择最佳的一个展示给用户。
But while asking the model to evaluate its own output might be useful for immediate feedback
但是，虽然让模型评估自己的输
出对于即时反馈可能有用，
I think it's probably unnecessary most of the time, especially if you're using a more advanced model like GPT-4.
但我认为大多数时候这可能是不必要的，特别
是如果您使用的是更先进的模型，如 GPT-4。
I haven't actually seen many people do something like this in production.
实际上，我还没有看到多少
人在正式产品中这样做。
It would also increase the latency and cost of your system,
这也会增加系统的延迟和成本，
because you'd have to wait for an additional call for the model.
因为您必须等待模型的额外调用。
And that's also additional tokens.
这也要消耗额外的Token。
If it's really important for your App product that your error rate is 0.0000001%,
如果对于您的应用产品来说，错误
率低于0.0000001%非常重要，
then maybe you should try this approach.
那么您可以尝试这种方法。
But overall, I wouldn't really recommend that you do this in practice.
但总的来说，我并不建议您在实践中这样做。
In the next video,
在下一个视频中，
we're going to put together everything we've learned in the evaluate input section, process section, and checking output section to build an end-to-end system.
我们将整合在评估输入部分、处理部
分和检查输出部分所学到的所有内
容，来构建一个端到端的系统。